<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark Feltner&#39;s Blog</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://blog.feltnerm.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.feltnerm.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 07:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 07:18:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Well then, first post here on the new static blog generator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why write a static blog generator?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, writing more. I want to do it. Becoming a better writer involves writing more, and having a blog is a great place to let out thoughts. I’d also like to have a permanent record of what I write, even if it’s backed up on some cloud-server somewhere in the ether-verse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I’m going to be writing more I would like to have ownership over what I write. I’m not saying this is common or going to happen to me, but I wouldn’t want something I wrote to be used commercially without at least my consent, and I certainly wouldn’t want someone attributing something &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; wrote to themselves. Not cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, I’m very ok with transparency in my writing process to the extent of open-sourcing &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/feltnerm/blog&quot;&gt;the generator&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/feltnerm/blog&quot;&gt;the posts&lt;/a&gt;. Feel free to submit an &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/feltnerm/blog/issues&quot;&gt;issue&lt;/a&gt; if anyone finds a spelling error or any other bug :P&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I love to build things and tinker with software. I’ve already spent more time building and fine-tuning the programmatic aspects of this blog than I have actually writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Writing, to me, is simply thinking through my fingers.
 - Isaac Asimov&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 14:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.feltnerm.com/posts/2013/11/17/First-Post!.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.feltnerm.com/posts/2013/11/17/First-Post!.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>posts</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
